ABDUR-ROHEEM SHERIF-DEEN

04, Engr. Olatunji Street, Destiny Homes Estate, Abijo, Ibeju-Lekki, Lagos, Nigeria · 08139781147

Email: abdurroheemsherifdeen@gmail.com · LinkedIn: abdur-roheem-sherif-deen

Twitter: @sir_simple_soul

I am a frontend developer proficient in HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript and ReactJs. I have 23 months experience working on individual projects such as my portfolio, Football livescore web app to mention less and also working with team of different tracks both design and backend team. I have led several projects to success such as kodeblog project and Daura project. I can work anywhere and ready to travel anywhere to work as well ready to improve my skill in other software development tools. I am a hardworking, motivated, and enthusiastic person with a proven record of accomplishment while working as the Admin officer at Ash-Shabab Schools and an Administrative Assistant, Jide Taiwo & Co as a surveyor and African Children Aid Education and Development Foundation (ACAEDF) as an admin assistant. I always strive to achieve the highest standard possible, at any given task and in any situation.

EXPERIENCE

25TH JUNE 2022 - 19TH JULY 2022

KODE BLOG WEB APP DEVELOPMENT (TEAM LEAD),

KODEHAUZ

Manage all team members from different to achieve the project goal of developing a blog website application for Kodehauz. Coordinate and assign tasks to the frontend team, review their submission and give feedback. As well as creating some UI/UX designs.

1ST NOVEMBER 2021 – TILL DATE

ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANCE/ IT PERSONNEL,

LAND OF HOPE (ACAEDF)

Manage administrative activities within the organization, staff recruitment, office management, staff management, social media management, data analysis, website management (WordPress) among others.

3RD DECEMBER 2020 – 21ST OCTOBER 2021 ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANCE (NYSC),

LAND OF HOPE (ACAEDF)

Manage administrative activities within the organization, staff recruitment, office management, staff management, social media management among others.

 4^{TH} MARCH 2020 – 13^{TH} MAY 2020

INTERIM SURVEYOR,

JIDE TAIWO & CO (VALUATION UNIT, ELEGBETA, LAGOS)

Property valuation for sales purpose, mortgage purpose and development. Rating and taxation of landed properties. Property rating, to know the tax rate payable by the owner of the property as well as property valuation, to arrive at a value at which a property can be sold in the market at a particular point in time.

2NDJANUARY 2019 – 4TH MARCH 2020

INTERIM SURVEYOR,

JIDE TAIWO & CO (IBEJU-LEKKI BRANCH)

Valuation and taxation. Conducting property sales, letting, management using both online, and offline means of marketing and communication. Was also responsible for the valuation of some given properties for the purpose of sales, mortgage and taxation.

12TH JANUARY 2015 - 30TH OCTOBER 2015

INTERNSHIP,

JIDE TAIWO & CO (LEKKI BRANCH)

Valuation and taxation. Conducting property sales, letting, management using both online, and offline approach.

21ST JULY 2011 – 30TH NOVEMBER 2013

ADMINISTRATIVE OFFICER,

ASH-SHABAB SCHOOLS

Coordinating all administrative processes, managing budgets, policies and events

EDUCATION

OCTOBER 2019

BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY (B. TECH),

FEDERAL UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY MINNA (FUTMINNA)

ESTATE MANAGEMENT AND VALUATION

NOVEMBER 2010

SENIOR SECONDARY SCHOOL CERTIFICATE (SSCE),

ASH-SHABAB SCHOOLS

CERTIFICATION

JULY 2022

FRONTEND DEVELOPMENT CERTIFICATE,

KODEHAUZ BOOTCAMP

MARCH 2022

FRONTEND DEVELOPMENT CERTIFICATE,

SIMPLILEARN

OCTOBER 2021

CERTIFICATE OF COMPLETION,

NATIONAL YOUTH SERVICE CORPS (NYSC)

FEBUARY 2019

BACHELORS DEGREE CERTIFICATE,

FEDERAL UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY MINNA (FUTMINNA)

APRIL 2016

CERTIFICATE OF ATTENDANCE,

NIESV CONFERENCE

OCTOBER 2010

CERTIFICATE OF PROFICIENCY IN DESKTOP PUBLISHING,

CYBERLINK MULTIMEDIA WORK-STATION

AWARD

OCTOBER 2021

DILIGENCY IN SERVICE AWARD,

LAND OF HOPE (ACAEDF)

NOVEMBER 2010

BEST GRADUATING STUDENT,

ASH-SHABAB COLLEGE

SKILLS

- HTML skill
- JavaScript skill
- Bootstrap Skill
- ReactJs Skill
- Tech savvy/ ICT skill
- Team work ability

- Online and Offline Marketing skill
- CSS skill
- Digital marketing skill
- Management skill
- Ability to work under pressure

REFERENCES

References will be provided on request.